{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Acoustic Ceiling Cleaning Services","__cache./api/resource/task/40188/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40188,"taskName":"Acoustic Ceiling or Wall Tiles - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean Acoustic Ceiling or Wall Tiles","xmTaskDescriptor":"Acoustic Ceiling Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":39,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Acoustic wood vaulted walls ceilings","textMessagingName":"Cln Acou Ceiling","rolloverLongDesc":"Acoustic tiles are made of soft, usually white, light-weight, porous material. Most often found in office ceilings, studios, home theaters \u0026 finished basements.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes deep cleaning of films such as smoke \u0026 grease.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean Acoustic Ceiling or Wall Tiles.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Clean an Acoustic Ceiling \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Acoustic Ceiling or Wall","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Acoustic Ceiling or Wall Tiles - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Acoustic Ceiling Project","urlName":"Acoustic-Ceiling-or-Wall-Tiles-Clean","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Acoustic Ceiling Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Acoustic,wood,vaulted,walls,ceilings,replacement,removal,Wall,Tiles,Clean,cleaner,Ceiling","emcCategoryOid":-12012,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":496,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40188/":{"taskOID":40188,"originalTaskOID":40188,"setID":496,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":767,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Type Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2776,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","answerDisplayText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move-out","answerDisplayText":"Move-out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","answerDisplayText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1534,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Completion of construction project","answerDisplayText":"Completion of construction project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5208,"questionDisplayText":"What to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be cleaned? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":605,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Acoustic tiles","answerDisplayText":"Acoustic tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3598,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lighting lenses","answerDisplayText":"Lighting lenses","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2969,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating/air grids","answerDisplayText":"Heating/air grids","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5918,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Speaker covers","answerDisplayText":"Speaker covers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6695,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Viny T-bar gridwork","answerDisplayText":"Viny T-bar gridwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3806,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Metal T-bar gridwork","answerDisplayText":"Metal T-bar gridwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5209,"questionDisplayText":"Why Clean","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2782,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General dirt and grime","answerDisplayText":"General dirt and grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6904,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains","answerDisplayText":"Water stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1631,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooking grease","answerDisplayText":"Cooking grease","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2564,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Food stains","answerDisplayText":"Food stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5822,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Smoke/Soot","answerDisplayText":"Smoke/Soot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4333,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Odors","answerDisplayText":"Odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":767,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Type Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2776,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","answerDisplayText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move-out","answerDisplayText":"Move-out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","answerDisplayText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1534,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Completion of construction project","answerDisplayText":"Completion of construction project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2776,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","answerDisplayText":"General cleaning (potentially recurring)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move-out","answerDisplayText":"Move-out","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","answerDisplayText":"Heavy cleaning (one-time event)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1534,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Completion of construction project","answerDisplayText":"Completion of construction project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5208,"questionDisplayText":"What to be Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be cleaned? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":605,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Acoustic tiles","answerDisplayText":"Acoustic tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3598,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lighting lenses","answerDisplayText":"Lighting lenses","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2969,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating/air grids","answerDisplayText":"Heating/air grids","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5918,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Speaker covers","answerDisplayText":"Speaker covers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6695,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Viny T-bar gridwork","answerDisplayText":"Viny T-bar gridwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3806,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Metal T-bar gridwork","answerDisplayText":"Metal T-bar gridwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":605,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Acoustic tiles","answerDisplayText":"Acoustic tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3598,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lighting lenses","answerDisplayText":"Lighting lenses","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2969,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Heating/air grids","answerDisplayText":"Heating/air grids","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5918,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Speaker covers","answerDisplayText":"Speaker covers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6695,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Viny T-bar gridwork","answerDisplayText":"Viny T-bar gridwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3806,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Metal T-bar gridwork","answerDisplayText":"Metal T-bar gridwork","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5209,"questionDisplayText":"Why Clean","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2782,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General dirt and grime","answerDisplayText":"General dirt and grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6904,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains","answerDisplayText":"Water stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1631,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooking grease","answerDisplayText":"Cooking grease","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2564,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Food stains","answerDisplayText":"Food stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5822,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Smoke/Soot","answerDisplayText":"Smoke/Soot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4333,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Odors","answerDisplayText":"Odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2782,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"General dirt and grime","answerDisplayText":"General dirt and grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6904,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains","answerDisplayText":"Water stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1631,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooking grease","answerDisplayText":"Cooking grease","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2564,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Food stains","answerDisplayText":"Food stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5822,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Smoke/Soot","answerDisplayText":"Smoke/Soot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mold/mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mold/mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4333,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Odors","answerDisplayText":"Odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}